

CONTACT

- **(**+57) 300 322 3023
- kcomtdaniel@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/daniel-kcomtfrontend-developer/
- https://portfolio-git-maindansaround.vercel.app/

LANGUAGES

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Typescript

FRAMEWORKS LIBRARIES

- Bootstrap
- React
- Tailwind

SOFT SKILLS

- Asertive communication
- Team work
- Problem solving mindset

EDUCATION

 Cum Laude in Social Communication

Universidad Monteávila 2012-2017

Daniel Kcomt

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a versatile and driven professional who loves creating amazing user experiences and solving technical challenges. I have skills in communication, radio and TV production, audiovisual specialization, and project management. I also taught myself frontend development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and ReactJS. I can troubleshoot and problem-solve using tools like Chrome DevTools.

I have excellent English communication skills and can use systems like Notion, HubSpot, Go High Level and Slack. I am open-minded, detail-oriented, responsible, and confident. I can work independently or in a team, meet deadlines, and learn from others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

2023 (Current)

Developed Personal Projects such as https://thexo.encolados.com using React. Website building for clients.

Tech Support

On The Fuze 2022-2023

Client training and support performed KPI analysis and optimized Landing Pages using GoHighLevel and Hubspot.

Freelance Web Developer

2020-2022

Created Landing Pages and Websites for individuals using Wordpress. Filmed and edited videos and executed marketing strategies.

VR Specialist

Uberflug Tech Marketing 2018-2020

Virtual Reality project management, leader of a 4-person work team. Photographer and developer of 360° virtual tours. And Wordpress Content creation.